

Divyanshu Gupta

Team Coach/Website Developer

Contact

+91 8932841719

itsdivyanshu799@gmail.com

Hardoi, India

Education

2020 - 2022

Master's Degree, MCA Chandigarh University I Present

2017 - 2020

Bacehlor's Degree, BCA Invertis University I Bareilly

2016 - 2017

12th.

Shri Guru Ram Rai Public School I Hardoi

2014 - 2016

10th,

Shri Guru Ram Rai Public School I Hardoi

Skills

Initiative Abilities

Communication	• • • • •
Computer Skills	•••••
Leadership	•••••
Adaptability	•••••
Content Writing	•••••
Critical Thinking	•••••
Gaming	• • • • •

About

Experienced Content Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry., Skilled in Web Content, Writing, Gaming and Web Design. Strong media and communication. Experience team leader and a Part-Time Gamer. A great storyteller, a bike enthusiastic person and a Fitness Fanatic.

Work Experience

Web Developer, Skiller V3

Jul 2019 - Present

Working as a Freelancer. Developed and designed many websites that have generated revenue for the client and have helped me in shaping my knowledge.

Field Organizer, Auto Expo 2020

Jan 2020 - Feb 2020

Served as the Field Organizer for the companies visiting the auto expo show.

Trainee, Ducat

May 2019 - Jul 2020

Worked as a Data Science trainee and gained knowledge in the coding part.

President, Invertia 2019 at Invertis University

Jul 2018 - Mar 2019

Served as the president for the social club of the Annual fest. lead the team of 5 members.

Certifications

Introduction to HTML, Coursera Sep 2020 - Nov 2020

Digital Skills, Accenture May 2020 - May 2020

Funding of Small Businesses, Mojoversity Jan 2020 - Mar 2020

GDG - Devfest India, Google Oct 2020 - Oct 2020

SEO Masterclass Webinar, Digital Deepak Nov 2020 - Nov 2020

Introduction to Git and Github, Prasanna Dubey(YT) May 2020 - May 2020

Android Workshop & Quiz Program, Aptron Aug 2018 - Aug 2018

PD Workshop, Invertis University | Sep 2019 - Sep 2019

Hobbies

- Speaking/Mentoring
- Learing Tips and Tricks
- Management
- Fitness

Languages

- HTML & CSS
- C/C++
- React Native
- Wordpress

Extra-Curriculum Activities

LAN Gaming, Jaipur National University Sep 2018 - Sep 2018

Won the tournament of LAN Gaming in CS 1.6

LAN Gaming, Jaipur National University Sep 2019 - Sep 2019

Won the tournament of LAN Gaming in CS 1.6

LAN Gaming, Invertis University Feb 2018 - Feb 2018

Awarded a certificate of 2nd position in LAN Gaming CSGO

LAN Gaming, Invertis University Feb 2020 - Feb 2020

Awarded a certificate of 1st position in LAN Gaming CSGO

Nukkad Natak(Drama), Invertis University Mar 2018 - Mar 2018

Awarded a certificate of 1st position.

Declaration

I hereby declare that the information provided above is true and to the best of my knowledge and belief.